spoilertv.co.uk 2016-12-02

# Site5 - Privacy Policy

## Legal / Privacy Policy

**We're committed to ensuring that we respect and protect our customers' privacy.**

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes what personal information of our customers (“Customers”) and visitors to the Site5 website (“Visitors”) (collectively, “Users”) is collected and how and when it might be used or shared by Site5.

## Who We Are

Site5 provides a variety of web presence solutions and related services (the “Services”). Site5 is a part of The Endurance International Group, Inc. (“Endurance”). [Learn more about the Endurance corporate family.](http://endurance.com/)

The Services offered by Site5 are hosted on servers located in the United States (U.S.) unless otherwise provided. By using the Services, you freely and specifically give Site5 your consent to export your information and data to the U.S.

## Information We Collect

We collect information in different ways from Users who utilize our Services, the network of websites accessible through our Services, or visit the Site5 website.

  * **Non-Personally Identifying Information.** When Users visit the Site5 website, Site5 collects non-personally-identifying information including the browser type, IP address, geographic location, language preference, referring site, metadata about the User’s use, the pages the User views and the date and time of each visit to the Site5 website.
  * **Personally Identifying Information.** Personally identifying information is any information that identifies you or would enable someone to contact you, which may include your name, email address, phone number and other non-public information that is associated with such information. It does not include aggregate information, anonymous information or any other non-personally identifiable information. The amount and type of personally identifying information that Site5 gathers depends on the nature of the interaction with the User. For example, we ask Visitors who choose to sign up for our newsletter for their name and email address while Customers are asked to provide additional information to process their purchases. Site5 may ask Customers to provide additional information beyond what was requested during their initial purchase if Site5 determines it is necessary to verify your identity or reduce fraud. Site5 does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described herein.
  * **Aggregated Statistics.** Site5 may collect statistics about a Customer’s use of the Services. For example, Site5 may collect the number of emails sent per month through the Services.

## Use of Information

We use the information we collect to provide the Services and as discussed in this section. 

  * **Non-Personally Identifying Information.** Site5 collects non-personally identifying information to better understand how Visitors use the Site5 website. Site5 may use aggregated and non-identifying information to promote advertisements that appear on the Site5 website and in connection with the Services.
  * **Personally Identifying Information.** The information collected from Customers is used to manage each Customer’s account and to promote other products or services that we believe may be of interest to the Customer. Site5 may also generate aggregate profiles from information that Customers provide during registration or subsequently as may be requested by Site5 (e.g. through customer surveys or additional services). 
  * **Emails.** If you have provided Site5 with your email address, Site5 may send you emails to tell you about new products or services, solicit your feedback, inform you of an outage or interruption in service, or just to keep you up to date with what's going on with Site5 and our products and services. If you send us a support request, we reserve the right to remove all personally identifiable information and publish such request on our website to help us support other Users.
  * **Passive Information.** Passively collected information, such as information collected from or about your device including through the placement of cookies (described in further detail below) or other tracking technologies (as mentioned below) is used to provide a customized experience as you use the Services.
  * **User Analytics.** Site5 may use the information it collects to do a better job of advertising and marketing our products and services, in connection with our security and compliance programs, to target prospective customers with our products or services, to assist us in offering you a personalized experience or otherwise tailor the Site5 website, product and service offerings to you.

## Sharing of Information

We may share personal information with the entities and brands within the Endurance corporate family to improve or offer new products or services that we believe may be of interest to our Users. We may also share personal information when we believe that such disclosure is required by law, to deliver a product or service, or as described below.

  * **Non-Personally Identifying Information.** Site5 may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate. e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
  * **Personally Identifying Information.** Site5 discloses personally identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that: (i) need to know such information in order to process it to provide the Services, and (ii) have agreed to keep such information confidential. Site5 will not rent or sell personally identifying information to anyone.
  * **Aggregated Statistics.** Site5 may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Site5 does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described herein.
  * **Law Enforcement and Special Cases.** Site5 or our service providers, may disclose personal information about Users, or information regarding your use of the Services in response to governmental or legal requests (such as to a subpoena, search warrant, or court order), or as otherwise required to comply with applicable laws. We may also disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against a party that threatens us, our systems or our Users (for example, to prevent a Distributed Denial of Service, or DDoS, attack).
  * **Sale of Business.** If Site5 is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a material portion of its assets that results in a change in corporate control, or insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any such change in ownership or use of your personal information as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.
  * **Domain Registration.** In certain jurisdictions or pursuant to the rules of the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN") or certain registries, the contact information you provide to register a domain name ("Domain Name Registration Information") has to be made available and accessible to the public through a "WHOIS" search. The WHOIS database is a publicly accessible database that lists the Domain Name Registration Information for a particular domain name, the name server(s) to which the domain name points, and the domain name's creation and expiration date. The Domain Name Registration Information you provide is hosted by us or a third party service provider and is made available to the public through WHOIS searches. At times, Customers may receive solicitations that result from searches of the publicly available WHOIS database by other companies or individuals. Any such solicitations or SPAM do not come from us and we do not control the use of WHOIS information by third parties. We may also deposit your Domain Name Registration Information with a third-party escrow provider to comply with ICANN requirements.

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain websites or open certain emails. Site5 uses cookies to help Site5 identify and track visitors, their usage of Site5’s website, and their website access preferences. More specifically, we use different types of cookies for different purposes: (i) "required cookies" are necessary for our website to work properly, (ii) "performance cookies" allow us to analyze how Visitors use our website so we can measure and improve the performance of our website, (iii) "functional cookies" allow us to remember choices you may have made on our website, and (iv) "advertising cookies" are used to present ads that are relevant to your interests. We may utilize cookies to track referrals from internal and external affiliates, as well as advertising campaigns. We may also use a third party service provider to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies may be used in those email messages to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and to enable us to provide more focused marketing communications to you. You may set your web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or change the settings on your web browser to clear or disable cookies. If you decide not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all of the features of our website. Additionally, please be aware that if you visit third party websites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your personal (i.e., contact) information. However, advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and are not responsible for information collected through them.

## Your Options

  * **Unsubscribe/Opt-out.** When you become a Customer you are automatically subscribed to receive transactional notices about your account, email newsletters and news of special promotions offered through Site5 and/or in conjunction with our partners. To unsubscribe from Site5 newsletters and promotional mailings, please update your preferences in your customer dashboard or submit a ticket in [Site5's customer area](https://customers.site5.com/supporttickets.php). You may also unsubscribe through the links provided in promotional email messages sent by us or our partners/affiliates. Customers are not permitted to unsubscribe from transactional notices.
  * **How to Access or Modify Your Information.** We allow you to access, update, and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in our custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. You may request access, updating and corrections of inaccuracies in your personal information we have in our custody or control by accessing your personal profile in your account or by contacting support via email. We may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records. To ensure you receive the information you need to manage your account and protect your privacy, please be sure to keep your contact and billing information up to date. You can contact Site5 support by email at [support@site5.com](mailto:support@site5.com).

## Modifications to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. However, if we plan to materially change how we plan to use previously collected personal information, we will provide you with advance notice prior to the change becoming effective and an opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. You can find when this Privacy Policy was last updated at the bottom of this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact: Legal Department, Site5, 2500 Ridgepoint Drive, Austin, TX 78754.

_Last Modified on: July 27, 2016_
